<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<items>
	<item>
		<content><![CDATA[
				
CAREER OBJECTIVE

•	Seeking an opportunity to become a part of a team comprised of creative and intelligent people whom value innovation, resourcefulness, an enjoyable work environment and dedication to achieving success.

SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS

•	IT Professional with 4 years’ experience in Website Design and Website Development.   And about 1.5 year experience in Software Engineering and QA Engineering. Have an extremely keen interest in website design/development and software industry. Eager to learn more skills and experiences. Fast learner and great problem solver. 
 
DEGREE RELATED SKILLS
 
•	Professional: 

	Web Design, Development and Programming 
	Web Systems Administration (Apache, Linux, UNIX, MySQL, PHP)
	Desktop Operating Systems and Applications
	Database Design and Query Optimization
	Search Engine Optimization
	Software testing 
	Online Business Development, marketing and Market Research 
	E-commerce applications
	IPhone, Android mobile apps development

•	Technologies: 	

	PHP (3, 4 and 5) + MySQL, Ajax, XML	
	XHTML / HTML, JavaScript(jQuery, Backbone, etc.), CSS
	Drupal, Wordpress, Joomla, Zen Cart, etc.
	SQL, Apache Web Server
	Zend Framework, CakePhp, Smarty Template Engine.
	Flash
	SEO, Google Analytics reporting and monitoring
	.NET 4.0, ASP.net, C#, JSP, ORACLE, SQL Server 2005+


•	Applications: 

	Adobe Creative Suite: Photoshop, Flash CS5 (Actionscript3.0), Dreamweaver, InDesign, Illustrator, Fireworks
	Microsoft Office: Word, Excel, Access, PowerPoint, Outlook, FrontPage.
	Zend Studio, Acrobat PDF, Eclipse, PowerDesigner, WampServer, IETester.
    
•	Operating system: 

Microsoft Windows (3.x, 95-98, ME, XP, 2000, Vista and MS-DOS), Mac OS X, Linux, CentOS, RedHat, Ubuntu, FreeBSD

PREVIOUS WORK AND EXPERIENCE

March 2012 – present
	Website designer/developer (Front and back ends)
Baomoney
http://baomoney.com.au/
Financial Services
Working for Baomoney which is the first professional financial website in Australia in Chinese language.
Responsibilities:

	Web maintenance 
	Developing new web functions and improving user experience 
	SEO.
	General technical support documentation.
	Technical skills used:

	Zend framework
	HTML5, CSS5, JavaScript
	Facebook, Sina weibo api
	Ajax
	Tomcat server

Dec 2011 – March 2012
	
Website designer/developer (Front and back ends)
Ecolink
http://ecolinkenterprise.com/
Food & Beverages industry

Worked as the primary web developer in Ecolink, helping build and grow the site to be one of the most popular food retail web sites on the Internet in Melbourne. 

Responsibilities:

	Web template design 
	Web maintenance 
	Telephone customer service
	SEO	Technical skills used:

	Wordpress
	LAMP Administration 
	CakePHP and Smarty template engine

Nov 2010 – June 2011
	Software engineer
Lian Cheng Science & Tech Co., Ltd  
http://www.sqiye.com/
Information Technology and Services industry
  Responsibilities:

	Using Manual Testing and Automation Testing Tools.
	Tested Linux, UNIX, Macintosh, and Windows software systems.
	Tested client-servers, networks, and updated operating systems.
	Prepared documentation, presentations, and ordeals to reduce bug issues.
	Documented bug errors, provided feedback on bugs, and worked with engineers to overcome barriers.
	Provided mobile support to user workstations.
	Well Acquainted With Software Development Life Cycle. Profound Knowledge in Software Testing Life Cycle. Knowledge on Quality Standards like ISO, CMM Levels.
 
April 2010 – August 2010
	
Website designer/developer (Front and back ends)
Shiny embroidery
http://winningspirit.info/
Clothing Industry

Worked as web developer in Shiny embroidery, one of the biggest Fabric Manufacturers in VIC, helping develop and update the current website. As part of the development team, was responsible for website development and SEO.

Responsibilities:

	Normalized database tables and performed extensive query optimization.
	Cleaned up and rewrote front end HTML and CSS to meet validation requirements to enhance interactivity
	Create banner ads, email advertisements / newsletters, and flash animations
	Created a clothes displaying web system with flash and PHP/AMF.
	
Technical skills used:

	.Net 4.0, ASP.NET, C#, SOA, WCF
	HTML5, CSS5, JavaScript
	MVC
	MS SQL Server
	Flash
	LAMP Administration

March 2010 – April 2010
	
Website designer  (Front end)
Oggetti Gifts
http://oggettigifts.com/
Import and Export

As part of the development team, programmed an e-commerce systems for a major Internet retailer. In addition to code development, maintained project documentation and assisted in application design.
Responsibilities:

	Provide internet related services including web site design, front-end web development, domain name registration, web hosting, search engine optimization / submission
	Handle all projects from start to finish, including administrative aspects
	Design visual layouts and graphics for web sites, including logo designs, flash animations and graphic design
	Provide troubleshooting and client support for email accounts
	Technical skills used:

	LAMP Administration 
	Web services – SOAP and REST
	Html, CSS, JavaScript

Feb 2010 – March 2010
	
Website designer  (Front end)
Advance Collection
http://advancecollect.com.au/
Import and Export
Responsibilities:

	Managed customer web development, web site hosting and e-mail, domain name registrations.
	HTML/CSS code. Flash design and development 
	Customer web sites consultation, content generation, edit, launch, search engine registration.

Nov 2009 – Jan 2010
	Website designer (Front end)
Lhamo
http://lhamo.com.au/
Import and Export 

Responsibilities:

	Created a dynamic flash user interface
	Updating the website content
	Communicating with our client from China.
	Involved in planning new issues and marketing initiatives.

July 2006 – June 2007
	
Year 12 math Teacher
San-hao high school

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

•	September 2009 – August 2010
ACS professional year program
Navitas

	Provisional Member of Australian Computer Society(ACS)
	BSB30107 Certificate III in Business

•	July 2007 – July 2009
Master of computer science (software engineer) 
MONASH University

	Created an online social websites by using ASP
	CISCO Certified Network Associate (CCNA) certificate
	As a part of group, created a traffic routing system using Java

•	July 2002 - July 2006
Bachelor of computer science and technology 
North University of China

	Created a supermarket web system and collage building simulation by using VRML (Virtual Reality Modeling Language) and Matlab
	First class prize in national mathematics competition in China

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES
 
	Reliable, motivated, hardworking and attentive to details.
	Strong written and verbal communication skills
	Excellent Time management skills
	Ability to show initiative and demonstrates good problem solving skills
	Highly motivated with the ability to work collaboratively to achieve shared goals

 ]]>



</content>
	</item>
</items>